

Anton Buriak

Talented Full Stack Developer

EDUCATION

V.N. Karazin Kharkiv National University (2018.4 - 2022.7) Bachelor's Degree Software Engineering, Computer Science

CONTACTS

- +380975940404
- antonburiak08@gmail.com
- (v) Hrushevskogo 35 Kostopil, Rivne 35001 Ukraine

SKILLS

Typescript

React.is Node.js **Angular** Vue.js Django Laravel Java Ruby on Rails Electron **AWS** Solidity

SUMMARY

Hello. Here is a professional software developer with hands-on experience in web development.

For last more than 5 years, I have developed many front-end/backend with high ratings and good feedback from the users. I successfully created these web sites and services in PHP(Laravel), Wordpress, Ecommerce, React.js, Vue.js, Node.js, Ruby on Rails, Python(Django), Java, MySQL, PosgreSQL, MongoDB and AWS. Of course, I have good experience in working as a team member. I am a full-time freelancer with good communication skills and my work is always perfect and high-qualified.

While working with you, I make sure the "Quality", "Speed", "Availability", "Co-operative" and "Honesty". Looking for a long-term, I am here to develop the websites for you who want to improve your idea and turn it into a live service.

WORK EXPERIENCE

FULL STACK DEVELOPR

VOXIPLAN

Sep. 2021 - Dec. 2022

Enterprise application similar to Calendly with Ruby on Rails, React.js, Typescript, Postgresql, TailwindCSS, Material UI and AWS.

FRONT END DEVELOPR

PIXELFIELD

Apr. 2020 - Aug. 2021

E-Learning web application with Vue.js, Nuxt.js, Typescript, React.js, TailwindCSS, Graphql as Frontend and Node.js, Django as Backend.

FULL STACK DEVELOPR

CREWPOND

Feb. 2019 - Mar. 2020

Booking & Renting web application with Node.js, Express.js, React.js, Vue.js, Typescript, MongoDB, Stripe and AWS.

FRONT END DEVELOPR

STOREONE

Apr. 2018 - Jan. 2019

Real Estate web application with React.js, Next.js, TailwindCSS, Graphql as Frontend and Ruby on Rails, Node.js as Backend.